My name's Conan Edogawa!
Meu nome é Conan Edogawa!
High school student Shinichi was forced to take a drug that shrunk him.
Shinichi, do ensino médio,
If the organization learned that Shinichi and Conan were the same person,
Se os criminosos descobrirem que somos a mesma pessoa,
everyone close to me would be in danger!
todos ao meu redor estarão em perigo!
The only one who knows the truth is Professor Agasa!
O único que sabe a verdade é o professor Agasa!
I hide my identity yet again today, in which there is only one truth!
Também escondi minha identidade neste dia, em que a verdade é única!
The first end of the century in 100 years
O primeiro fim de século em cem anos
When told to cry, I laughed instead
Quando me mandaram chorar, eu ri
The first end of the century in a long, long time
O primeiro fim do século em muito, muito tempo
We're leaping into a wide open world
Estamos saltando rumo a um mundo aberto
The things I tried to understand as a child
As coisas que eu tentava entender quando era criança
remain a mystery even as an adult
Continuam um mistério para mim como adulto
I'm neither a hotshot nor especially great
Não sou um figurão nem grande coisa
All I understand is the pounding of my heart
Eu só entendo as batidas do meu coração
It's neither an answer nor the truth
Não é uma resposta, tampouco a verdade
All I have faith in is the pounding of my heart
Eu só acredito nas batidas do meu coração
That and nothing else
E nada mais
Robberies, kidnappings, murders...
Roubos, sequestros, assassinatos...
There's just no end to these crimes...
Esses crimes não têm fim...
That's exactly why your detective skills are proving so useful.
Por isso mesmo suas habilidades investigativas vêm sendo úteis.
Old man Kogoro gets all the credit, though.
Mas o velho Kogoro leva todo o crédito.
All done! These are my special Criminal Pursuit Glasses.
Prontinho! São os óculos de perseguição criminal!
How do I use these?
Como se usa?
Try pressing the button on the side.
Aperte o botão do lado.
Sweet!
Demais!
It'll display the location of this transmitter within a 20-kilometer radius.
Ele mostra a localização deste transmissor
You can keep it here most of the time.
Pode mantê-lo aqui na maior parte do tempo.
It's like a sticker!
É como um adesivo!
Thank you, Professor Agasa!
Obrigado, professor Agasa!
My name is Masami Hirota!
Meu nome é Masami Hirota!
Please! Find my father!
Por favor, encontre o meu pai!
Go on...
Certo...
My father, who works away from home in Tokyo, quit his taxi driver job,
Meu pai, que trabalha em Tóquio, largou o emprego de taxista
and he's been missing for a full month now!
e está desaparecido há um mês!
So that's why you've come to me?
Então por isso você veio me procurar?
Yes.
Sim.
I took time off from school in Yamagata to come look for him here!
Tirei uma folga da minha escola em Yamagata para vir procurá-lo!
You're the only one I can turn to now, Detective!
Sei que posso confiar em você, detetive!
Very well. I'll take on the case.
Muito bem, aceito o caso.
This is my father, Kenzo Hirota.
Este é meu pai, Kenzo Hirota.
He's 5'9" and 48 years old!
Ele tem 48 anos e 1,70 m de altura!
What about this cat?
E esse gato?
It's my father's cat. Its name is Kai.
É Kai, o gato do meu pai.
He has three others named Tei, Gou, and Ou.
Ele tem três outros gatos: Tei, Gou e Ou.
Finding people isn't really my thing.
Encontrar pessoas não é meu ponto forte.
But if he had one of these on him, I could've found him in no time at all.
Mas se ele tivesse um desses,
I know! I'll stick it on Ran and test it out!
Já sei! Vou colocar na Ran para testar!
Here you are.
Aqui está.
What the heck are you doing?!
O que você está fazendo?!
Oh, nothing...
Ah, nada...
The transmitter!
O transmissor!
Oh no! I stuck it there!
Essa não! Eu grudei ali!
My mother died when I was little, so my father is my only family!
Minha mãe morreu quando eu era pequena,
If anything were to happen to him!
Se algo acontecer com ele...
No. Well, not yet...
Não, bem, ainda não...
I haven't found any leads...
Ainda não achei nenhuma pista...
Sorry.
Desculpe.
Masami-san again?
Era a Masami de novo?
That's the third time today.
É a terceira vez hoje.
Apparently he didn't socialize much with other people,
Parece que ele não socializava muito
and he almost never talked about himself, according to his coworkers.
e quase nunca falava sobre a própria vida, segundo os colegas.
Goukai Teiou pulls ahead of the pack to earn his 5th G-1 victory in a row!
Goukai Teiou passa na frente
Goukai Teiou? (Heroic Emperor)
Gou-kai Tei-ou?
It's my father's cat. Its name is Kai.
É Kai, o gato do meu pai.
He has three others named Tei, Gou, and Ou.
Ele tem três outros gatos: Tei, Gou e Ou.
Kai, Tei, Gou, and Ou!
Kai, Tei, Gou e Ou!
Rearrange them and...
Se mudar a ordem fica...
This is...
Assim...
...nothing important.
...nada de mais.
Goukai Teiou truly is invincible!
Goukai Teiou é invencível!
Yeah, that has to be it!
Sim, só pode ser isso!
Hirota-san loves horse races!
O Hirota é fã de corridas de cavalo!
So he named his cats after a famous horse!
Então ele deu o nome dos gatos inspirado no cavalo!
Hey, Dad!
Ei, pai!
Hey, now!
Ei, ei!
I bet you can find him at the race track!
Aposto que dá para encontrá-lo no jóquei!
Hello?!
Alô?
Wow! This is my first time at a race track!
Nossa, é a primeira vez que venho no jóquei!
Let's hurry and find Masami-san's father.
Vamos achar logo o pai da Masami.
Yeah, right! Like he'd be that easy to find!
Até parece que vai ser tão fácil assim!
Don't be mocking us detectives!
Não menospreze detetives como nós!
There he is!
Ali está ele!
See! I'm such a great detective!
Viu só? Sou uma grande detetive!
No way!
Sem chance!
I'll go get him!
Vou chamá-lo!
Wait! He's purposely gone missing.
Espere, ele sumiu de propósito.
We don't want to scare him away and then lose him!
Não queremos assustá-lo e fazê-lo fugir!
But...
Mas...
We'll follow him back home.
Vamos segui-lo até a casa.
I've been looking for you for so long!
Eu te procurei por tanto tempo!
Dad!
Pai!
Good for her!
Fico feliz por ela!
Doesn't something seem different about her?
Não tem alguma coisa diferente nela?
She's wearing more grown-up clothes,
Ela está usando roupas mais adultas
and it looks like she has makeup on.
e parece que está com maquiagem.
She hasn't seen her dad in a long time!
Faz tempo que ela não vê o pai!
Of course she'd wear make up!
É claro que ia se aprumar!
That case was as easy as pie in the hands of Kogoro Mori!
O caso foi moleza nas mãos de Kogoro Mori!
Who's that?
Quem é esse?
He's dead?!
Ele está morto?
We found him after he hanged himself last night.
Nós o achamos depois que ele se enforcou ontem à noite.
What a pain!
Que saco!
What about his daughter?!
E a filha dele?
Daughter?
Filha?
You know, Hirota-san's daughter? The one who came looking for him?
Sabe, a filha do Hirota? A que o procurou.
Oh? So there was something going after all?
Ah, então tinha mesmo alguma coisa acontecendo?
Something wasn't right about him.
Algo nele não parecia certo.
He said he'd pay me a full years' worth of rent all at once
Disse que pagaria o aluguel do ano todo de uma vez
if I let him have an apartment with no questions asked.
se eu não fizesse perguntas.
Plus all the bills were brand new and crisp!
Além disso, todas as notas estavam novinhas!
My guess is if his daughter did come over, then she's probably dead too.
Se a filha dele veio,
What do you mean? I thought Hirota-san committed suicide...
Como assim? O Hirota cometeu suicídio...
The police said it was a murder.
A polícia disse que foi assassinato.
Yes, it was a homicide.
Sim, foi homicídio.
He was hung from the ceiling after he was killed.
Ele foi pendurado do teto depois de ser morto.
Judging from the large hand marks on the victim's neck,
A julgar pelo tamanho das marcas de mãos no pescoço da vítima,
the murderer must have been quite a large man.
o assassino devia ser um homem bem grande.
What about his daughter?!
E a filha dele?
These were lying on the floor near the scene of the crime.
Isso estava no chão, perto da cena do crime.
These are Masami-san's glasses.
São os óculos da Masami.
Her body hasn't turned up yet, but I'm pretty sure that she's...
O corpo dela ainda não foi encontrado,
Come on, now. Don't be so depressed.
Qual é, não seja tão pessimista.
But Masami-san might've been murdered!
Mas a Masami pode ter sido morta!
And she just found her father, too! How horrible!
E ela acabou de achar o pai! Que horror!
We still don't know for sure that she was murdered!
Ainda não temos certeza se ela foi morta!
We can't give up yet!
Não desista!
But now what? If only we had a clue to go by!
Mas e agora? Se pelo menos houvesse alguma pista!
That's it! I accidentally put the transmitter on her!
Já sei! Sem querer, eu pus o transmissor nela!
Perfect!
Perfeito!
Hey, kid! Where are you going?!
Ei, garoto! Aonde você vai?
The fact that it's moving means Masami-san might still be alive!
Como está se movendo,
Come on! Make it in time!
Vamos lá! Chegue a tempo!
A pachinko parlor?! What's Masami-san doing here?
Um pachinko? O que a Masami está fazendo aqui?
Oh no, the battery's dying!
Essa não, a bateria está acabando!
I have to find her quick!
Tenho que encontrá-la logo!
Ain't no kids allowed in here!
Aqui não é lugar de criança!
Get out!
Se manda!
The battery's dead.
A bateria acabou.
Hey, you! Why were you gone so long?!
Ei, você! Por que sumiu por tanto tempo?
Oh, you know...
Ah, você sabe...
What's up with Ran?
O que houve com a Ran?
She's been like that for a while now.
Ela está assim faz um tempo.
She must really be worried about Masami-san.
Deve estar muito preocupada com a Masami.
Something's weird about that guy.
Tem algo estranho com aquele cara.
He's been looking up here this whole time.
Ele está olhando pra cá faz tempo.
He's the man who was hanging out by Hirota-san's apartment!
Ele que estava perto do apartamento do Hirota!
Come to think about it, the killer was a large man!
Falando nisso, disseram que o assassino era um homem grande!
He killed Masami-san's father?
Foi ele que matou o pai da Masami?
Wait right here! I'll go catch him and find out where Masami-san is!
Espere aqui! Vou pegá-lo e descobrir onde a Masami está!
Where's Masami-san? What's happened to her?!
Cadê a Masami? O que houve com ela?
Tell me!
Espere aí!
I caught him!
Peguei!
Good work!
Bom trabalho!
What great luck! Who'd have thought the killer would come to us?!
Que sorte! Não pensei que o assassino viria até nós!
Killer?! You've got it all wrong!
Assassino? Você entendeu tudo errado!
Yeah, right! Then who are you?!
Me engana que eu gosto! Então quem é você?
I'm the same as you!
O mesmo que você!
What?!
O quê?!
I'm a detective too!
Também sou detetive!
Actually, I, too, was asked to find Hirota-san.
Na verdade, também pediram que eu encontrasse o Hirota.
By this man.
Foi este homem.
That's that guy!
É aquele cara!
I'm really a detective, I swear!
Juro que sou detetive!
Then why did you run away?!
Então por que fugiu?
That young woman came after me, so I instinctually...
Aquela jovem veio atrás de mim, então, por instinto...
I've always been sort of a coward...
Sempre fui meio covarde...
I wear these sunglasses so people can't make fun of me.
Uso os óculos escuros para não tirarem sarro de mim.
Enough of your stupid excuses!
Chega de desculpas esfarrapadas!
Get serious! Masami-san's life is at stake here!
Leve isso a sério, a vida da Masami está em perigo!
Yes, I know.
Sim, eu sei.
So you were asked to locate Kenzo Hirota-san as well, then?
Então você também foi contratado para encontrar o Kenzo Hirota?
Yes. But there was something strange about his family...
Sim, mas tinha algo estranho com a família dele...
This was the man who hired me!
Esse é o homem que me contratou!
He asked me to find his brother who left Kyushu for Tokyo.
Pediu que eu encontrasse o irmão dele, que veio para Tóquio de Kyushu.
He said his brother was his only relative.
Disse que o irmão era o único parente dele.
His only relative?
O único parente?
Masami-san was supposed to be Hirota-san's only relative!
Era pra Masami ser a única parente dele!
That's weird, too! Masami-san's father came here from Yamagata!
Que estranho! O pai da Masami veio de Yamagata!
That is strange.
Estranho mesmo.
There can't be two Hirota-sans...
Não pode haver dois Hirotas...
There's one other thing that's strange.
Outra coisa também é estranha.
I heard this from the taxi company that Hirota-san worked at.
A empresa de táxi na qual o Hirota trabalhava me disse algo.
Apparently he would drive the same route every single evening,
Parece que toda noite ele fazia o mesmo trajeto
without bothering to pick up any passengers!
sem pegar nenhum passageiro!
And he would do this at breakneck speeds!
E ele pisava fundo no acelerador!
He was just letting off steam.
Ele estava só desestressando.
Happens all the time to middle-aged men.
É normal com homens de meia idade.
So, who is this client of yours?
Então, quem é o seu cliente?
Akira Hirota. 28 years old. He's a large man, over 6 feet 3 inches tall.
Akira Hirota, 28 anos. É um homem grande, com mais de 1,90 m.
A large man?!
Um homem grande?
That's right.
Isso mesmo.
Could he be the large man the inspector was talking about?
Será que é o homem grande de quem o detetive estava falando?
Tell me! Did you tell this man anything about Hirota-san?!
Ei, você contou alguma coisa sobre o Hirota para esse homem?
Yes, of course...
Sim, é claro.
And then it was after that that Hirota-san was murdered.
E depois disso o Hirota foi morto.
So I wondered if there was any connection...
Será que há alguma ligação?
That's it! This man murdered Hirota-san!
Minha nossa! Esse homem matou o Hirota!
And then he took Masami-san with him!
E levou a Masami!
Well? How can I contact him?!
Então, como podemos entrar em contato com ele?
He contacts me!
Ele entra em contato comigo!
So you don't have any clues?
Então você não tem nenhuma pista?
Sorry...
Sinto muito.
It's him!
É ele!
There's no mistake! It's the man I ran into at the pachinko parlor.
Não há dúvidas, é o homem que vi no pachinko.
But why did the transmitter on Masami-san's watch lead me there?!
Mas por que o transmissor da Masami me levou até lá?
If he really is the killer, and he was wearing Masami-san's watch...
Se ele for mesmo o assassino e estava usando o relógio da Masami...
...then she's already...
...então ela já...
...been murdered!
...está morta!
Hurry and recharge it, Professor!
Recarregue logo, professor!
Stop rushing me! Being impatient isn't going to help you any!
Pare de me apressar! Não adianta nada ser impaciente!
But if we don't hurry...
Mas se não nos apressarmos...
Say, do you remember the robbery from the other day,
Ei, você se lembra do roubo do outro dia,
the one where they stole a billion yen?
o outro de um bilhão de ienes?
Yeah, the one with the trio of thieves?
Sim, do trio de ladrões?
A security guard was killed when he recklessly tried to stop them.
Um segurança foi morto quando tentou impedi-los.
That's what he got for taking them lightly.
Isso que dá subestimar criminosos.
Calm, cool, and collected...
Calmo, frio e consistente...
That's your style, isn't it?
É o seu estilo, não?
I get it.
Eu sei.
Is he really in this hotel?
Ele está mesmo neste hotel?
Definitely! I saw him go in on my way home from school!
Com certeza! Eu o vi quando estava voltando para casa!
That's strange! The transmitter hasn't moved at all for a while now!
Que estranho! Faz tempo que o transmissor não se move.
He didn't take the watch off and escape, did he?!
Ele não fugiu sem o relógio, fugiu?
Yes, he's staying in Room 802.
Sim, ele está no quarto 802.
Come on, hurry up!
Vamos, depressa!
Who'd have thought he was really here?
E pensar que ele realmente estava aqui.
Just when I'm in a hurry, too!
Justo quando também estou com pressa!
Thank you!
Obrigada!
Open up! I know you're in there!
Abra! Sei que você está aí!
It's open!
Está aberto!
He's dead!
Está morto!
This sweet smell... it's potassium cyanide!
Esse cheiro doce... É cianeto de potássio!
I see. He couldn't live with what he had done so he killed himself!
Entendi, ele não conseguiu viver com seus pecados e se matou!
We should contact the police!
A gente tem que chamar a polícia!
That's Masami-san's watch.
É o relógio da Masami.
So he did take it from her.
Então ele pegou dela.
Empty duralumin cases.
Maletas de duralumínio vazias.
Wait!
Espere!
Two separate, yet conflicting requests to find the same person...
Dois pedidos distintos, mas conflitantes,
Kenzo Hirota-san acting strange and driving the same route everyday...
Kenzo Hirota agindo estranho, fazendo a mesma rota todo dia...
And then these cases...
E essas maletas...
What if...
E se...
Huh? Hirota-san was single?!
Hã? O Hirota era solteiro?
Yeah. He didn't have any daughters.
Sim, ele não tinha filhas.
Plus he was born and raised in Tokyo.
Além disso, nasceu e foi criado em Tóquio.
That can't be!
Não pode ser!
That's it! I have this case figured out!
É isso! Já entendi o caso!
These empty cases are the key to unlocking this mystery!
As maletas vazias são a chave do mistério!
Masami-san, Kenzo Hirota, and Akira Hirota...
Masami, Kenzo Hirota e Akira Hirota...
Now that we know they're not relatives,
Agora que sabemos que não eram parentes,
they have no connection whatsoever!
não há relação entre eles!
But in the context of the other recent incident,
Mas levando em conta o outro incidente recente,
the entire mystery comes unraveled!
todo o mistério se revela!
They're the three thieves who stole the one billion in yen!
Eles são os três ladrões que roubaram um bilhão de ienes!
Judging from the number of cases here,
A julgar pelo número de maletas,
they must have been filled with the stolen money.
elas deviam estar cheias do dinheiro roubado.
If so, then the reason Hirota-san sped down the same route every day
Assim sendo,
was to rehearse their getaway!
era para ensaiar a fuga!
Their plan succeeded, but he took all the money for himself and ran.
O plano deu certo, mas ele pegou todo o dinheiro e fugiu.
He betrayed them.
Ele os traiu.
Eager to catch Hirota-san, the two partners concocted lies
Sedentos para encontrá-lo, os dois inventaram mentiras
and sent separate detectives to locate him.
e enviaram detetives diferentes para achá-lo.
And then when he was found, he was killed.
Então, quando ele foi encontrado, foi morto.
Killed by the large man, who was then killed in this very room.
Morto pelo homem grande, que foi então morto neste quarto.
Killed by the woman who claimed she was Hirota-san's daughter.
Morto pela mulher que disse ser a filha do Hirota.
Perhaps she was the mastermind behind these murders!
Talvez ela tenha sido a mente por trás dos assassinatos!
Wait!
Espere!
Her hairstyle and overall appearance were different,
O cabelo e a aparência estavam diferentes,
but her build and the number of suitcases she had weren't!
mas a fisionomia e o número de maletas não!
Where are you going, Conan-kun?!
Aonde você vai, Conan?
I found Masami-san!
Eu achei a Masami!
Ran! Hurry!
Ran, depressa!
Hey, kid! No cutting in line!
Menino, sem furar fila!
Our dad's gonna be chopped into pieces and buried alive in the mountains
Nosso pai vai ser fatiado e enterrado vivo nas montanhas
if we don't hurry and save him!
se não o salvarmos logo!
G-Go right ahead...
Podem ir...
Follow that taxi!
Siga aquele táxi!
What about the mountains?
E as montanhas?
The reason she seemed different the second time we saw her
Ela estava diferente na segunda vez que a vimos
was because when we found Hirota-san,
porque, quando achamos o Hirota,
she was in a hurry and hadn't completed her disguise!
ela estava com pressa e não tinha terminado o disfarce!
And then Hirota-san's reaction when he saw her...
E a reação do Hirota quando a viu...
That wasn't because he was surprised to see his daughter.
Não foi surpresa por ver a filha,
It was because he was terrified of the partners he betrayed
mas medo dos parceiros que ele traiu vindo atrás dele por vingança!
Damn it! Why didn't I realize it sooner?!
Droga! Por que não percebi antes?
What now? We lost her!
E agora? Nós a perdemos!
I'm 100% certain she entered this harbor!
Estou certo de que ela entrou nesse porto!
She's definitely somewhere nearby!
Ela com certeza está por perto!
Conan-kun!
Conan!
Where's the money, Masami Hirota?
Cadê o dinheiro, Masami Hirota?
Or should I say, Akemi Miyano-kun.
Ou melhor dizendo, Akemi Miyano.
Okita-san! What's going on?!
Okita! O que está havendo?
The sleeping drug you gave me to put him to sleep...
O remédio de dormir que você me deu para que ele dormisse...
The instant he drank it, he fell to the ground and stopped moving!
Assim que ele bebeu, ele caiu no chão e parou de se mexer!
Explain!
Explique-se!
What he had in brute strength he lacked in intelligence.
O que ele tinha de força, não tinha de inteligência.
There's no doubt that he would alert the authorities
Sem dúvidas que, assim que ele pegasse o dinheiro
by throwing all his money around the instant he got it.
sairia gastando adoidado, alarmando as autoridades.
As long as someone that dangerous remained alive,
Enquanto alguém perigoso assim ficasse vivo,
my own plans would be hindered.
meus planos seriam prejudicados.
You intended to kill everyone from the start, didn't you?!
Desde o começo sua intenção era matar todos, não era?
Now hand over the money.
Agora passe o dinheiro.
It isn't here! It's being held at a certain location.
Não está aqui! Está em um lugar seguro.
I'm sick of you using me!
Estou cansada de você me usando!
I'm through with this!
Chega disso!
Do you honestly think that is an option?
Acha mesmo que você tem escolha?
I do.
Acho.
After I escape overseas, I'll let you know where the money is.
Depois que eu fugir pro exterior, te aviso onde o dinheiro está.
We can't have that, now. As long as you're alive, my plan is in jeopardy.
Não posso aceitar isso.
Once you're dead, all links to me will have vanished.
Quando você morrer, todas as ligações vão sumir.
I can easily find any number of replacements for you and the other two.
Para mim, é fácil achar substitutos para você e os outros dois.
Getting my own hands dirty goes against my principles,
Sou contra sujar minhas próprias mãos,
but it will be the finishing touch.
mas será o toque final.
How simple-minded.
Que simplório.
Kill me and you'll never know where the money is.
Se me matar, você nunca vai saber onde o dinheiro está.
I have a pretty good idea where to find it.
Tenho uma boa ideia de onde encontrar.
You did a good job. Allow me to express my gratitude by killing you.
Você fez um bom trabalho.
Masami-san!
Masami!
Take this!
Toma essa!
Are you alright?
Você está bem?
Just a scratch.
Pegou de raspão.
You're the boy from the detective agency!
Você é o garoto da agência de detetive!
How did you know I was here?!
Como sabia que eu estava aqui?
My transmitter!
Meu transmissor!
Transmitter?
Transmissor?
When we first met at the agency, I accidentally stuck it on your watch.
Quando a gente se viu na agência,
After following the signal, I arrived at the hotel and then ran into you.
Depois de seguir o sinal, cheguei ao hotel e encontrei você.
Seeing you with all the large suitcases,
Ao ver você com todas aquelas maletas,
I realized you were leaving with the billion yen that you stole.
percebi que estava saindo com o um bilhão de ienes roubados.
Who are you?
Quem é você?
Conan Edogawa. A detective.
Conan Edogawa, um detetive.
I had no idea there was anything on the watch.
Eu não sabia que tinha algo no relógio.
But the watch belonged to that big man, right?
Mas o relógio era do homem grandão, não?
No, he broke his own watch when he lost control and killed Hirota-san,
Não, ele quebrou o próprio relógio
so I gave him mine.
Então eu dei o meu.
This guy intended to kill everyone from the very start, didn't he?
Esse cara pretendia matar todos desde o começo, não é?
Yes.
Sim.
Hirota-san realized this,
O Hirota percebeu isso,
so he betrayed us before we knew what was happening.
então nos traiu antes de entendermos a situação.
Does that mean this man is the mastermind behind the billion-yen robbery?
Quer dizer que esse homem
That's right. Okita scouted for people he needed to realize his plan.
Isso mesmo.
He would put these people into teams and have them commit robberies.
Ele formava equipes
Rumor had it that he would eliminate his recruits to keep them silent
Havia boatos de que ele eliminava os recrutados para silenciá-los
after they would finish his jobs,
depois que o trabalho terminava, mas não achei que era verdade!
You're not going to run away?
Você não vai fugir?
I'm tired.
Estou cansada.
I'll tell you where the suitcases with the one billion yen are!
Vou dizer onde as maletas com o dinheiro roubado estão!
The front desk of the hotel, right?
Na recepção do hotel, não é?
How did you know that?!
Como sabe?!
When you got in the taxi, you didn't have the suitcases with you.
Quando você entrou no táxi, você não estava com elas.
I simply assumed that...
Eu presumi que...
You're really something.
Você é mesmo incrível.
That's enough!
Já chega!
You talk too much, woman!
Você fala demais, mulher!
Masami-san!
Masami!
Who's he?!
Quem é ele?
The boss behind the billion yen robbery!
O chefe por trás do roubo de um bilhão!
Just as she had said, the billion yen was being kept at the hotel.
Como ela disse, o dinheiro estava na recepção do hotel.
The bill codes matched those of the stolen money.
As notas coincidem com o dinheiro roubado.
Thus the billion-yen robbery case came to a close.
E com isso, o caso do roubo de um bilhão de ienes foi encerrado.
Thank you, little detective.
Obrigada, detetive mirim.
Just my imagination
Só impressão minha
Playing with threads around my finger while drinking lukewarm tea
Brincando com fios entre os dedos bebendo chá morno
Let's walk lightly to the bossa nova rhythm
Vamos caminhar levianamente ao ritmo da bossa nova
The puzzle pieces are in my hands
As peças de quebra-cabeça em minhas mãos
That's right...
Isso mesmo...
I was in the same place last week but with different clothes
Semana passada eu estava no mesmo lugar, mas com roupas diferentes
Step by step, there's no reason to be anxious
Passo a passo, não tem por que ficar ansioso
Case by case, I don't care if you laugh
Caso a caso, tudo bem se você rir
Beyond the countless days, she's waiting for me
Além dos dias incontáveis, ela espera por mim
I gotta go my own way
Tenho que seguir meu próprio caminho
Up there!
Ali em cima!
The shot came from the top of the building across the river!
O tiro veio do topo do prédio do outro lado do rio!
What does this coded number message say?!
O que essa mensagem codificada diz?
They could be road numbers!
Podem ser números de estradas!
Like Route 162, you know?!
Como Nacional 162!
Get this helicopter moving, Inspector!
Ponha o helicóptero para correr, detetive!
On the next Conan--
No próximo episódio de Conan...
Next Conan's Hint:
Dica do próximo Conan:
Take a good look at a regular electronic calculator.
Dê uma boa olhada numa calculadora normal.
Next episode, try reversing your thinking.
Vamos tentar ver do jeito oposto!